qataronlinedirectory.com 2019-03-26

# Privacy Policy | Qatar Online Directory.

**Trans Media International W.L.L.** is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you might provide via the websites powered by us. This is to explain our privacy policy on how we manage the information received.

You acknowledge and agree that we may collect information about you. The information may be obtained from:

You may decide whether to provide any information we seek from you. However, if you do not provide it, we may not be able to provide our services to you effectively.

You may seek information we hold about you from the website and ask for any details that are wrong to be corrected. We may require to use the information for related activities of Trans Media International WLL or its sister concerns, but we will not disclose it to third parties without your consent.

We may share or transfer the information in our databases if required by law to disclose the information, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this website, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, closure or similar event.

We keep your personal data only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal requirements.

In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our servers and our databases are protected by industry standard security technology, such as industry standard firewalls and password protection.

Our employees who have access to personal data have been trained to handle such data properly and in accordance with our security protocols and strict standards of confidentiality. Although we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorised disclosure, alteration or destruction of data, we will try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

To assist us in providing the best possible results from [www.qataronlinedirectory.com](http://www.qataronlinedirectory.com/staging/) for both users and advertisers, we occasionally need to gather information about how people use the site. The information collected by cookies enables us to decipher user preferences & patterns thus providing valuable insight into improving the quality of the services we provide to you. You can choose to disable all cookies by managing your browser preferences. For most browsers this can be done via "Options" or "Preferences" under one of your browser menus.

Our websites contains links to other sites. Those sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites since we do not control them.

Our websites contains links to other sites. Those sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites since we do not control them.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of www.qataronlinedirectory.com, such as acquisition by or another company, a user's personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

The site has been designed to be user friendly to the end user. We always strive to enhance the portal and increase the accuracy of the product to the highest level.

Trans Media International WLL, employees, agents, & representatives are not liable for any damages relating to errors or omissions which may occur in an advertisement or listing or which may appear or fail to appear here except where a specific charge has been made. In such cases Trans Media International WLL liability shall be limited to the specific charge for such advertisements or listings.

Changes & updations are made periodically in order to ensure the accuracy of the information provided in the site. However, the accuracy of that information depends to a large extent on the information you provide. In order to maintain accuracy of your company information, we suggest the below:

By using our site or services, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy statement. Trans Media International WLL may decide to change this privacy policy from time to time. Any change applies from the time it is published and will be updated here so that you are always aware of it.

If you have any questions about our privacy policies, please feel free to [**contact us**](http://www.qataronlinedirectory.com/staging/pages/contact-us.php) at [www.qataronlinedirectory.com](http://www.qataronlinedirectory.com/staging/)

  1. **Your Personal Information**
    * Personal information provided voluntarily when registering online.
    * From sources of information which are generally available to the Public.
    * Website usage information through tracking your click pattern on our sites.
    * Cumulative data, measuring traffic to our websites but not relating to you personally.
  2. **Access to, disclosure & correction of your information**
  3. **Security of Database**
  4. **Cookies**
  5. **Links to Other Sites**
  6. **Third Party Sites**
  7. **Sale of Business**
  8. **Accuracy of Information**
    * Go through your company’s information at regular intervals and let us know if there are any changes required in the information provided.
    * Keep us up to date with changes to personal information such as your name or address  by contacting us through Company updation form / Free Listing Form  / Brand Listing Form given in  [www.qataronlinedirectory.com](http://www.qataronlinedirectory.com/staging/)
  9. **Changes to this Policy**
  10. **Contact Details**
